Melich, Tanya M.; Papers apap079
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Melich Publications, Speeches, and Editing Work, 1957-2007; 12; 1.4 cubic ft.
  - Materials for Thomas E. Dewey Biography—Excerpts From Michigan Paper 1859-1926, 1959 (Box 1 (12-Melich Publications, Speeches, and Editing Work), Folder 6)
  - Materials for Thomas E. Dewey Biography—Dewey interview with Harlan B. Phillips, 1957 (Box 1 (12-Melich Publications, Speeches, and Editing Work), Folder 7-15)
  - Speeches, 1988 (Box 1 (12-Melich Publications, Speeches, and Editing Work), Folder 16)
  - Speeches, 1991 (Box 1 (12-Melich Publications, Speeches, and Editing Work), Folder 17)
  - Speeches, 1991 (Box 1 (12-Melich Publications, Speeches, and Editing Work), Folder 18)
  - Yankelovich Background reading, 1982 (Box 1 (12-Melich Publications, Speeches, and Editing Work), Folder 19)
  - Yankelovich Chapter 1-2, 1985 (Box 1 (12-Melich Publications, Speeches, and Editing Work), Folder 20)
  - Yankelovich Chapter 3-4, 1985 (Box 1 (12-Melich Publications, Speeches, and Editing Work), Folder 21)
  - Yankelovich Chapter 5-6, 1985 (Box 1 (12-Melich Publications, Speeches, and Editing Work), Folder 22)
  - Yankelovich First Drafts and Outlines, 1983-1984 (Box 1 (12-Melich Publications, Speeches, and Editing Work), Folder 23)
  - Yankelovich First Drafts and Outlines, 1983-1984 (Box 1 (12-Melich Publications, Speeches, and Editing Work), Folder 24)
  - Yankelovich Interview—Aspin, 1984 (Box 1 (12-Melich Publications, Speeches, and Editing Work), Folder 25)
  - Yankelovich Interview—Betty Friedan, 1984 (Box 1 (12-Melich Publications, Speeches, and Editing Work), Folder 26)
  - Yankelovich Interview—David Cohen, 1984 (Box 1 (12-Melich Publications, Speeches, and Editing Work), Folder 27)
  - Yankelovich Interview—George Lodge, 1984 (Box 1 (12-Melich Publications, Speeches, and Editing Work), Folder 28)
  - Yankelovich Interview—Leon Shapiro, 1984 (Box 1 (12-Melich Publications, Speeches, and Editing Work), Folder 29)
  - Yankelovich Interview—Samuel D. Proctor, 1984 (Box 1 (12-Melich Publications, Speeches, and Editing Work), Folder 30)
  - Yankelovich Manuscript, 1984 (Box 1 (12-Melich Publications, Speeches, and Editing Work), Folder 31)
  - Yankelovich Notes, 1984 (Box 1 (12-Melich Publications, Speeches, and Editing Work), Folder 32)
  - "Youth Politics: A Study Cliques Within the Association of New York State Young Republican Clubs, 1932-1959," Melich Thesis., 1961 (Box 1 (12-Melich Publications, Speeches, and Editing Work), Folder 33)
  - "Youth Politics: A Study Cliques Within the Association of New York State Young Republican Clubs, 1932-1959," Melich Thesis., 1961 (Box 2 (12-Melich Publications, Speeches, and Editing Work), Folder 1-2)
- New York State Republican Family Committee, 1974-1995; Undated; 15; 4.8 cubic ft.